Konvitz, Milton R. Papers /4039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Academic Files
  - Sub-Series 2. Subject Files
    - Cornell: Housing. (Box 198, Folder 46)
    - Cornell: Independent Counsel. (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Cornell: Independent Counsel. (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Cornell: Mimeographed Announcements. (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Cornell: Mimeographed Announcements. (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Cornell: Mimeographed Announcements. (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Cornell: Miscellaneous. (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Cornell: Miscellaneous. (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Cornell: Miscellaneous. (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Cornell: Miscellaneous., 1979 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Cornell: Mott (John R.) Centennial Committee. (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Cornell: Mott (John R.) Centennial Committee. (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Cornell: Reports on College of Arts and Sciences., 1965 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Cornell: Reports on College of Arts and Sciences., 1965 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Cornell: Social Science Research Center. (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Cornell: Society for the Humanities. (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Cornell: Special Commission to Investigate the Events of April 4, 1968. (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Cornell: Strike. (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Cornell: Student Appraisal of Teaching and Courses. (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Cornell: Students for Education. (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Cornell: Tuition Exchange Plan. (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Cornell: Undergraduate Education. (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 29)
    - Cornell: Unrest., 1969 (Box 199, Folder 30)
    - ILR: Alumni Data. (Box 199, Folder 31)
      Confidential
    - ILR: Catherwood, Martin P. (Box 199, Folder 32)
      Program Planning Memos.
    - ILR: Catherwood, Martin P. (Box 199, Folder 33)
    - ILR: Committee on International Activities. (Box 199, Folder 34)
      Windmuller's Group
    - ILR: Committee on International Activities. (Box 199, Folder 35)
    - ILR: Committee on International Activities. (Box 199, Folder 36)
    - ILR: Committee on Masters of Industrial and Labor Relations Comprehensive Examination. (Box 199, Folder 37)
    - ILR: Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics. (Box 199, Folder 38)
    - ILR: Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics. (Box 199, Folder 39)
    - ILR: Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics. (Box 199, Folder 40)
    - ILR: Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics. (Box 199, Folder 41)
    - ILR: Curriculum. (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - ILR: Curriculum. (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - ILR: Curriculum. (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - ILR: Curriculum. (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - ILR: Curriculum. (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - ILR: Dean's Office. (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - ILR: Dean's Office. (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - ILR: Dean's Office. (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - ILR: Dean's Office. (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - ILR: Department of Collective Bargaining. (Box 200, Folder 10)
      Minutes
    - ILR: Extension. (Box 200, Folder 11)
      Mimeographs
    - ILR: Extension. (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - ILR: Graduate Faculty. (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - ILR: ILR News (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - ILR: ILR News (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - ILR: ILR Review. (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - ILR: Labor Law Research Project. (Box 200, Folder 17)
      Damage Suits
    - ILR: Library. (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 19)
      General
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - ILR: Mimeographed Memos. (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - ILR: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - ILR: Office Procedures. (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - ILR: Personnel Office. (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - ILR: Personnel Office. (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - ILR: Personnel Office. (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - ILR: Personnel Office. (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - ILR: Research Committee. (Box 201, Folder 5a)
    - ILR: Staff Personnel Policies Committee. (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - ILR: Student Body Data. (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - ILR: Teaching at ILR. (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - ILR: Undergraduate Program Committee. (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Law: Admission of Foreign Students. (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Law: Admission of Foreign Students. (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Law: Admission of Foreign Students. (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Law: Forrester, Dean William Ray. (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Law: Forrester, Dean William Ray. (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Law: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Law: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Law: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Law: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Law: Minutes of Faculty Meetings. (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Law: Miscellaneous. (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Law: Miscellaneous. (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - Law: Miscellaneous. (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Law: Miscellaneous. (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - Law: Thoron, Willcox, et al. (Box 201, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Publications. (Box 201, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 3. Lectures/Notes
    - American Ideals, 1954 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      Spring 1954.
    - American Ideals, 1957 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      Fall 1957.
    - American Ideals, 1958 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      Fall 1958.
    - American Ideals, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 6)
      Fall 1960.
    - American Ideals, 1962 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      Fall 1962.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1953 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      Fall 1953.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1953 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Development of American Ideals, 1953 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Development of American Ideals, 1954 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      Fall 1954.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1957 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      Spring 1957.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1957 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Development of American Ideals, 1959 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      Spring 1959.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 15)
      Spring 1960.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1960 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Development of American Ideals, 1961 (Box 202, Folder 17)
      Spring 1961.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1961 (Box 202, Folder 18)
      Fall 1961.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      Fall 1963.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1964 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      Spring 1964.
    - Development of American Ideals, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 3)
      Fall 1965.
    - Elements of Law. (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Jurisprudence, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Jurisprudence, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Jurisprudence, 196 (Box 203, Folder 7)
      Fall 1966.
    - Labor History. (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Labor Law, 1967 (Box 203, Folder 9)
      Spring 1967.
    - Labor Law Seminar, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      Spring 1963.
    - Labor Relations: Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Patterns of Thought. (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Theories: Work, 1960 (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 4. Course Outlines
    - Course Descriptions, etc. (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - ILR 22: American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - ILR 22: American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - ILR 23: Elements of Law. (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - ILR 59: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - ILR 290: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - ILR 290: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - ILR 290: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - ILR 291: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - ILR 291: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - ILR 291: Development of American Ideals. (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - ILR 300: Labor Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - ILR 300: Labor Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 26)
    - ILR 300: Labor Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 27)
    - ILR 502: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 28)
    - ILR 502: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 29)
    - ILR 502: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - ILR 600: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 31)
    - ILR 600: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 32)
    - ILR 600: Labor Relations Law and Legislation. (Box 203, Folder 33)
    - ILR 651: Theories of Industrial and Labor Relations. (Box 203, Folder 34)
    - Postgraduate Course in Civil Rights. (Box 203, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 5. Student Papers
    - Drunkenness. (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Education. (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Education. (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Employment-Unemployment Discrimination. (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Government and Poverty. (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Government and Poverty. (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Government and Poverty. (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Health. (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Indians. (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Insurance. (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Legal Aide - Needs. (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Legal Aide - Needs. (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Migrant Workers. (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 204, Folder 26)
    - Negative Income Tax. (Box 204, Folder 27)
    - Negroes. (Box 204, Folder 28)
    - Poverty Programs. (Box 204, Folder 29)
    - Slums. (Box 204, Folder 30)
    - Urban Renewal. (Box 204, Folder 31)
    - Welfare - Social Services. (Box 204, Folder 32)
    - Welfare - Social Services. (Box 204, Folder 33)
    - Welfare - Social Services. (Box 204, Folder 34)